I was so scared of saying I am a woman
and then instantly hearing no you&#39;re not
because in my head I fought with that
every day
this episode is sponsored by better help
online therapy visit betterhelp.com
Padilla because sometimes existing is
exhausting and if you want to watch this
episode completely ad-free no sponsors
and completely uncensored click the join
button down below to become a member
anyway hello Chris hello Anthony you
have been a part of Mr BEAST&#39;s video
since the Inception pretty much
basically I was there when he created
the channel
um I was his first subscriber were you
also his bestie bestie yeah we grew up
uh we sat at the same lunch table we
were kind of the only kids who talked
about like YouTube and video games so a
bunch of nerds yeah yeah you know the
Nerds but so we would hang out
afterwards film videos together and we
just fell in love with doing it yeah
yeah I feel like the earliest videos you
guys made really were capturing that
that friendship yeah it was just us just
doing whatever we could think of it
because there was no rules back then
there was no like algorithm or anything
it was just whatever you could film put
it on YouTube and the videos have blown
up to the point where now they are
consistently getting over 100 million
views each
and which is just I can&#39;t even fathom
what like how many people that looks I
can&#39;t either and you are in almost every
video yeah you kind of became Chris the
guy from Mr Beast exactly it was
actually for the longest time my Twitter
bio was the guy in Mr Beast videos and
then about a year and a half ago it
turned into sometimes I&#39;m a Mr Beast
video oh so the guy part was removed it
was yeah that was removed a long time
ago like was that anticipating yeah that
was going to detach from that identity
yeah so for me in my head I was like oh
people are gonna instantly start asking
questions if I did that because like
when you&#39;re trans you think everybody
knows you&#39;re trans yeah it&#39;s like when
you&#39;re high yeah it&#39;s exactly like it
but so I took it out and I was like oh
no people are gonna know people are
gonna nobody ever said anything so I was
like that was my first step and I was
like okay okay all right let&#39;s keep
going yeah I feel like about how many
maybe six months to a year ago I started
to see a change in your appearance yes
you started to look a little bit less
masculine a little bit less beardy yeah
at the exact same time you look like you
were glowing like you were more excited
like your posture was better like you
were like excited about life yeah it was
weird I didn&#39;t realize how unhappy you
looked beforehand yeah looking up old
pictures of you I searched old pictures
of you and and you could see a dramatic
shoe but it wasn&#39;t a real smile it was
it was a and it was a performance smile
I mean because like was I sad every
single day during those times no but
like in the back of my head it was
something I constantly felt like I
wasn&#39;t being true to myself I wasn&#39;t
being true to the people who were fans
of me because I was hiding my true self
from them and the thing that was really
keeping me for so long away from like
who I truly am is how people would react
I was so scared of like I&#39;m from a small
town in a conservative area so when I
was younger I was like this is my this
little bubble is my entire world how
will they react then I got a little
older guy I was like maybe maybe one day
and then I got famous and my bubble went
from this small little town to hundreds
of millions of people you&#39;ve had a lot
of people speculating on your gender
yeah you know just you growing out your
hair you I mean today you you showed up
fully I did presenting I did as a woman
I did because I am a woman oh
[Music]
you&#39;ve never said that before I&#39;ve never
said that publicly enough but I I&#39;ve
been fully like confident in that
decision for over a year now
um I kind of my idea was to kind of play
catch up with the internet in the way
that I discover myself like you were
talking about
um you know six seven eight months ago
my hair started growing out all those
kind of things I wasn&#39;t quite sure
exactly who I was yet but I knew I was
not cisgender
um so I needed the freedom to be able to
express myself and be able to figure out
who I was and so for a while I was
trying gender fluid I was like what what
is making me feel like I&#39;m by gender
what is tying me to this you know
masculinity and really it was after a
lot of talking with the therapist and a
lot of like self uh reflection I
realized it was really just the societal
pressure of your Christmas Mr Beast
you&#39;re the guy that starts the fires
you&#39;re the guy that builds the stuff you
know and like my whole life I&#39;ve enjoyed
doing those things but I&#39;ve never really
felt like the guy yeah and that becomes
so intrinsically connected with who you
are that it felt like it was shattering
everything exactly and I was scared that
people would think that I&#39;m magically
gonna become a different person but for
me I I have no like I&#39;m very proud of
who I was and how I&#39;ve gotten here it
took me a long time to get here yeah but
I&#39;m finally here so I I&#39;m not ashamed of
all of that or anything I&#39;m actually
really proud of it there&#39;s been a huge
huge reaction to this like people are
like their minds are blown as something
like this happens I knew there was going
to be a big reaction but I thought it
would stay like you know like in that
YouTube you know everything it&#39;s like
tabloid culture now it&#39;s like every
single thing has some kind of headline
about you and what it means scenes and
the effects on Mr Beast and all these
different things it was crazy I was
trying to take a break I was like okay I
it&#39;s not affecting me too bad but I
don&#39;t need to consume all this media and
attention of myself I&#39;ll delete all my
social media and then I get on Google
and I go to open a new tab and Google
will recommend me articles about myself
but you love Mr Beast and Chris Tyson
and here&#39;s this thing about people
hating you please stop I don&#39;t want to
know about it yeah so we&#39;re just
constantly being fed uh articles with
headlines that are just blatantly wrong
right their lives and not only it&#39;s like
it wasn&#39;t all hate and it wasn&#39;t all
support it was it was from both sides
but there was also like a lot of people
just uh you know they don&#39;t really know
how to talk about trans people so
instantly they&#39;re like Chris Tyson comes
out as a trans woman good for them even
though you just said HRT yeah I&#39;m like
no I didn&#39;t no I didn&#39;t yeah yeah until
today yeah until today with Anthony I
mean I feel like we should
take a moment on that like how does that
feel publicly saying in front of cameras
that you are a woman I for the longest
time to even say it to some of the
closest friends it would make me like my
hands shake to say I would get so
nervous but now I can say I&#39;m a woman
I&#39;m happy to say I&#39;m a woman it&#39;s
something that&#39;s honestly so freeing and
I think that is part of what the HRT did
for me was being able to accept myself
and being able to look in the mirror and
say yes you are a woman every single
person has something about themselves
that they kind of
want to be more of yeah you know and
then they&#39;re insecure about yeah even if
it is just lacking confidence even if
it&#39;s just I want to be a little bit more
confident in myself yeah here you are in
front of hundreds of millions of people
who have been criticizing you for every
single reason in the book and you&#39;re
focusing on the way that you feel when
you are most true to yourself yeah I
mean if you&#39;re if you&#39;re away to
confidence is to wear a dress wear a
dress if your weight of confidence is to
get so swole you look like a bodybuilder
do that is that you&#39;re talking about
Jimmy yeah Jimmy is getting really small
isn&#39;t it he&#39;s pumping yeah you see his
Twitter he is Jack he is Jack you&#39;re
getting there man out of nowhere until I
get my hands on him oh and not Chris
affect him watch out the Chris effect
isn&#39;t that why all that people say
there&#39;s the Chris effect the Carl effect
like one person can can change or like
infect the other brains and the other
friends I mean I&#39;ve always joked that
there and I hate that people will clip
it but there is a smidgen of truth to it
because Carl came down to North
Carolina&#39;s small town and he had bright
pink hair yeah and I was I was like
how do you have the confidence to like
go to the grocery store and not feel
like every single person is staring at
you and he&#39;s like I don&#39;t care and I was
like what what you could not care what
others think you can just not care right
I didn&#39;t get the update you know there
is
a little bit of Truth to the idea that a
friend can come into a circle and they
can show you what confidence looks like
yeah they can show you what true
confidence is because for a while like I
was like yeah I guess I&#39;m confident but
it was all fake it wasn&#39;t all real and
then I saw somebody come in and be
themselves and I was like I want that I
want to be myself and even though like I
saw people make fun of Carl because of
his hair he would just shrug it off that
was like I I can do that maybe maybe
give it a couple years you hear that
Carl you inspired someone you did it you
mentioned taking hormones and you
mentioned that it saved your life yes
for so long every day I I would go to
bed and I would have dreams vivid dreams
I was a woman like my whole life and I
would wake up in the morning and it was
just like getting ripped out of a
reality that I didn&#39;t want to be taken
out of so it was like the dream was a
reality yeah there was times where I
would just lay in bed all day and just
sleep because it was more fun to do that
or more enjoyable to me to do that
because the real world I didn&#39;t feel
connected to it I&#39;ve really never felt
connected to my body until I started
taking HRT and like I was amazed like
after two three weeks I just started
having a mental Clarity that it felt
like a fog that had been around me just
went away and I could see things clearly
I could feel confident in who I was I
knew who I was finally surely truly
without a shadow of a doubt and that is
what really saved my life because for
the longest time you know like in 2017
2018 I started gaining weight I got
really depressed because I pretty much
thought that there was no way I was
going to be able to transition ever and
I was just going to have to keep
marching forward in a life I didn&#39;t want
to live and I was just gonna have to
keep doing that until I couldn&#39;t do it
anymore what was the internal battle
like the thing I really felt hatred
towards was myself for not understanding
myself also internalized transphobia
just made me feel you know there&#39;s not a
lot of trans people in in general but
there&#39;s also not a lot of trans people
in my area so the only exposure I had to
trans people and trans issues were from
you know the other end of the spectrum
and so I started to hate myself I was
like oh I&#39;m I&#39;m pretending I&#39;m lying I I
like and it took me so many years of I I
ran away I pretended it didn&#39;t exist
multiple times I threw away every single
pair of clothes I ever owned I went to
conversion therapy oh yeah like you
really did not want to be what you felt
at your core was your true self I
thought it was a curse for all of my
life and it wasn&#39;t until I started
taking HRT that I was like this is
this is not a curse it&#39;s a blessing like
I I can finally be myself or did you
have a moment when you first realized
that the way that you identify with your
gender was different than what was
expected of you I was six years old my
sisters went to Camp my parents were in
the living room I told my parents that I
was going to build a popsicle stick
airplane in my room and then I went to
my sister&#39;s room and went in their
closet and grabbed as much stuff as I
can and locked my door and I turned on
Arthur and it was an episode where there
was ballerinas and I just pretended to
be a ballerina and danced around my room
and from that moment on I was like I
don&#39;t know what this is but I know I
need to hide it because I don&#39;t think
the people I I don&#39;t remember exactly
what made me hide it at such a young age
but I think it was just like you know
growing up in that area going to you
know a very like um very very religious
well all churches are religious but this
one was
religious XXL yeah yeah it was the
premium and because like the biggest
thing is for me I was such a
forward-facing person that any kind of
changes were instantly going to drum up
questions and so like for me that&#39;s why
I was so glad that even though I had
during this time when I put out that I
was on HRT I was very sure I was a trans
woman I was not ready to come publicly
out yet so I was very happy that like
people were encompassing me into the
gender uh into gender fluid because that
is what I had identified as a while and
and that gave me that ability to dress
more feminine and people not be like are
you a girl or what&#39;s your gender what&#39;s
your gender yeah I mean do you feel like
old Chris is dead dead
dead buried Hatchet all of it all of it
gone I mean you still have uh the
reminders through the videos that will
be permanently online for the rest of
Eternity that&#39;s what I say to people who
were like but I missed the old Chris and
I looked up to you hey go watch the
videos they&#39;ll be there forever was it
more difficult for you to come out to
yourself or to others myself
far more once I came out to myself it
was I came out to myself with my
therapist and and it took like
it took like three therapy sessions
where I was like I&#39;ve known this for a
long time I I&#39;m I&#39;m pretty sure and then
I was you know I I I know like and then
I was like I am a woman and it was it
was hard for me to say that because I
was so scared of saying I am a woman and
then instantly hearing no you&#39;re not
because in my head I fought with that
every day that&#39;s the conversation you
were having with yourself there was a
voice in the back of my head that just
hated me everything I did hated me and
it wasn&#39;t until like I started accepting
myself and being kind to others and like
just listening to what my body wanted
like that&#39;s when that voice started
going away started taking HRT haven&#39;t
heard from that voice in a very long
time where do you think that part of you
is gone I think it&#39;s I hope it&#39;s locked
away do you think it&#39;s disappeared oh
entirely yeah that little piece of it
you must feel like you have so much more
like access to the to your whole self
without that part of you shutting you
down constantly I literally had people
within the first like couple of months
of like me coming out to like private
like friends and like my therapist
starting HRT they were like you&#39;ve just
been talking so much more and you just
seem so much more present in the
conversation and I was noticing that
myself too because like I would get done
with conversations and be like why is my
jaw hurt so bad oh I was talking and
smiling I was talking and smiling I
haven&#39;t done that in a while I mean even
now I feel like people who have watched
you for a long time will see that change
in you wanting to express your thoughts
wanting to express your emotions it
doesn&#39;t matter now if I want to express
them or not they just freely come out of
me because I don&#39;t suppress them anymore
and that is what&#39;s truly the best part
of it is that I can just like what comes
out of my mouth is me now and it&#39;s
nobody else influencing me it&#39;s nobody
telling me I have to be this person it&#39;s
me coming out do you remember the first
time that you looked at yourself and you
were like that is me I&#39;m not ashamed of
that anymore I did I was actually
heading to the studio to go film and I
was driving my car and I had something
in my eye and I pulled down my mirror
and I just looked at myself and for the
first time it like hit me that I was
like I&#39;m looking like myself and I just
started crying while driving and I had
to pull over yeah you&#39;re like this this
looks like how I I feel how I see myself
and my dreams yeah and I&#39;ve had so many
moments leading up to them like even
when I went dress shopping today I
accidentally cried a little bit because
I put on this dress and I was like oh I
gotta love this I feel like you know
whether anyone watching is trans or not
like there&#39;s there&#39;s it&#39;s such a
relatable feeling to want to be a truer
version of yourself and to to run away
from that for a certain amount of time
for any reason yeah
how does it feel you know like this
you&#39;re constantly finding all these
things that make you feel more and more
true to yourself I&#39;ve always been myself
I&#39;m now taking ver uh I&#39;m now taking
steps to make sure I&#39;m the like best and
happiest version because there was a
point in my life where and a lot of
people thought that was the best version
of me because that&#39;s the only thing they
had ever seen Chris from Mr Beast but I
was very unhappy and I was tired and I
was miserable and now I&#39;m like just I
wake up every day and I&#39;m like what are
we doing today I wake up at 7 30. I used
to wake up at 11 30 every single day you
wake up with excitement I wake up it was
excitement I&#39;m like what are we doing
today what&#39;s going on like you get to
live life yeah I I another day of being
trans that for me it&#39;s like the best
thing why do you think the the news of
you taking HRT and you looking more
feminine why do you think it went so
viral because it&#39;s a really hot button
issue right now there&#39;s a lot of people
putting in their two cents about it and
then I think what really like made a lot
of people focus on it was that I&#39;m just
like I&#39;m just living my life I&#39;m not
saying anything or doing anything I&#39;m
just hey I&#39;m on HRT I&#39;m a lot happier
now and um I think that in my opinion A
lot of people were like no we can&#39;t have
somebody this successful in this like
happy being on HRT it&#39;s bad Optics so I
mean if that&#39;s the reason maybe it was
just general transphobia maybe they just
don&#39;t like me oh maybe they&#39;re not Chris
fans they might they might be big Nolan
fans so you&#39;re not taking it too
personally though no I I know that at
the end of the day like even the people
that are riding these like crazy
articles about me are probably just you
know normal people that are going home
to see their wife and kids or whatever
they&#39;re doing their jobs I&#39;m doing my
job but that&#39;s why I wanted to come to
your show to be able to get a hold of my
narrative again right because you you
lost control of the narrative control
every like ever everyone had an opinion
that had nothing to do with what your
actual thoughts are I know apparently I
sued people I did it
and they were like Chris is suing me and
then I quote tweeted it and I was like
you better be ready this is my lawyer
and it was a picture of Jimmy with like
sideways sunglasses and people took that
as serious There&#39;s real life
consequences to false things being made
up about you yeah then you have people
making YouTube videos saying that your
decision to be yourself and to openly be
yourself is destroying Mr Beast and it&#39;s
gonna mess up the business and you
should have thought about that I I
should have thought about that that&#39;s
all how dare you ruin the business by
being your true self how dare you exist
it was kind of weird to see people be
like oh now Jimmy&#39;s put in between a
rock and a hard place where he obviously
doesn&#39;t want to support Chris but the
left would be so mad if he didn&#39;t and
I&#39;m like all these speculation all these
crazy things I told Jimmy like seven
years ago I walked out of my bedroom it
was late I walked out and it was kind of
one of those
and then he was like we don&#39;t have to
talk about it if you don&#39;t want to wait
what was it that that gave it away fully
dressed up oh so you&#39;re dressing up as a
woman long before yeah we lived oh I&#39;ve
been I&#39;ve been dressing up as a woman
since I was like six years old
I guess dressing up as a girl now I
messed up as a woman yes but you walked
out Jimmy sees you yes dressed up as a
woman yes and he goes we can talk about
this if you want and I was like no
um did you turn around and go into your
room and we didn&#39;t talk about it Jimmy
is really good about if you don&#39;t want
him to bring something up he&#39;ll never
mention it ever again but um it was
about three years ago we were all
hanging out and we were having a good
time
um you know on the channel we like to
say we&#39;re having some apple juice and uh
just drinking some good stuff drinking
some apple juice and there was one
moment I was sitting around all the guys
and I had I had just been really like
thinking all that day about like my
gender and everything and combined with
the Apple Juice I just blurted out to
them I don&#39;t want to be a man anymore
just out of nowhere out of nowhere in
front of all of them and then started
like crying and the the support I got
from them in that moment was like that&#39;s
when I knew I was like okay like I have
my friends back everybody else like
that&#39;s all you have the support from
your core group yeah they&#39;re really like
my family do you remember just like what
it felt like to have that out there to
feel like I&#39;m lying to like my best
friends we know everything about each
other like and I&#39;m like this is a huge
part of me and I want to tell them but
like it I&#39;m even so scared to tell them
like even when I used to try to form the
words I would just lock up and couldn&#39;t
talk about it because I was so terrified
to like out myself yeah because there&#39;s
so many
so many things that you consider to be
negative that would come out of that
yeah and now I realized that was all an
internalized transphobia my friends
would have accepted me I probably could
have gotten through the process a little
faster yeah but everybody grows at their
own pace and
becomes themselves when they do I mean
you see all these comments on the
internet and no matter how many positive
ones that are there the positive ones
don&#39;t exist but then the negative ones I
think it&#39;s because there&#39;s a little bit
of fear attached to the implications or
what else they might be thinking like
those things sit with you and you
accidentally find thousands or in your
case because you have hundreds of
millions of people watching and judging
and commenting on every single thing
that you do you&#39;re likely to see tens of
thousands of comments yeah and sometimes
the algorithm can just be a butt and
just send you all the hates and one one
Fell Swoop but also it&#39;s like you have
to realize that when people are sending
those messages I mean I I was a crappy
kid on the internet I used to be a mean
kid people say those things because
they&#39;re also struggling with things I
would my whole life I was struggling
with my identity who I was I hated
myself like
so every time I see one of those like
hate comments or like people saying mean
things in my DMs I&#39;m like I know that&#39;s
probably somebody who&#39;s going through
something and I just it doesn&#39;t really
bother me I used to see people living
the life I wanted to live and I would
get jealous and angry at them and
because and like they get to live this
life and they get to be celebrated and
you know like obviously you don&#39;t see
the hate they get but it&#39;s like they&#39;re
not getting any hate and all this kind
of stuff and and you get into that
mindset but then you realize oh that&#39;s
just me just like pointing all that back
at myself and using somebody else as a
Target do you feel like after coming out
and feeling like you can actually be
your truest identity
in addition to not having to hide
something about yourself do you feel
like you&#39;re more
aware and present like do you feel like
instead of living like through with
tunnel vision because you&#39;re blocking
out all of this that&#39;s in your
brain do you feel like now you have
access to more of you I do I post way
too much on the internet because I&#39;m
just so excited to authentically be
myself and be like this is me hey
everybody the person you knew for a long
time that was like a facade a fake
version of me this is the real me I&#39;m
still the same person I just look a
little different I mean yeah you&#39;re
carrying you&#39;re caring more about things
it seems you&#39;re caring about your
fashion your now makeup your hair you
know you&#39;re you&#39;re caring about your
health it seems like you just seem
healthier all around yeah I&#39;m drinking a
lot more water too oh okay that&#39;ll do it
that&#39;s that&#39;s everything that&#39;s the
secret to life the secret to life is
water yeah oh and then I will poop more
than once every six days
oh you should definitely be doing that
oh yeah okay good to know so here&#39;s a
really quick fun fact did you know that
hydrating is super important even if
you&#39;re not running a marathon and if
that&#39;s your first time hearing that I
need to have just a really quick word
with the American Education System
liquid IV is the number one powdered
hydration brand in America and now it is
completely sugar-free and yes it does
still hydrate you two times faster than
water alone I&#39;ve seen many people
commenting things on these videos saying
things like Anthony interviewing people
for eight hours a day and sitting on
your ass talking to them for such a long
time that&#39;s that feels like it&#39;s an
athletic Endeavor I agree with them it
definitely is because that is 100 fact I
gotta say my favorite flavor is a white
peach flavor with green grape being a
very very close second real people real
flavor real hydrating now sugar-free
grab your liquid IV hydration multiplier
sugar-free and bulk nationwide at Costco
or get 20 off when you go to liquid
iv.com and use code Padilla at checkout
that&#39;s 20 off anything you order order
we&#39;re going to use a promo code Padilla
at liquid iv.com this episode is also
sponsored by Better Health oftentimes in
life we&#39;re faced with tough decisions
and the path forward isn&#39;t always clear
while it may be helpful talking with
your friends a therapist&#39;s clinical
awareness can offer grounded insight and
guidance so whether you&#39;re dealing with
decisions around your career
relationships or anything else therapy
helps you stay connected to what you
really want while you navigate life
trusting yourself to make decisions that
align with your values is like anything
the more you practice it the easier it
gets as many of you may know by now I&#39;ve
been a huge proponent of therapy since I
started going about six years ago which
has been hugely helpful for me in my own
struggles with anxiety and depression so
if you&#39;ve been thinking about starting
therapy better help might be perfect for
you it&#39;s 100 online all you have to do
is fill out a brief questionnaire and
you&#39;ll be matched with the licensed
therapist plus you can switch therapists
at any time for no additional cost let
therapy be your map with better help
visit betterhelp.com Padilla to get 10
off your first month that&#39;s betterhelp
h-e-lp
p.com slash Padilla you mentioned that
you changed your the spelling of your
name from Chris CH the Chris it&#39;s okay
with a K so just to feel a little bit
more feminine about it I actually have
always liked how it looked with a K it
is cooler I used to I had I apparently I
didn&#39;t know this and I&#39;m probably going
to uh crack a bunch of eggs in the
audience oh but
um if you have an online Persona where
you present as a different name and
present as a female that&#39;s just being
trans online you&#39;ve been out as trans
online like wait in what way like in the
same way of like you&#39;ve kind of came out
you haven&#39;t come out officially but you
came out in a space to where it was safe
people don&#39;t know who you actually are
so you&#39;re like anonymously you&#39;re yeah
you&#39;re kind of anonymous anonymously
coming out as trans so is the Chris with
a K an online only name do you have a
separate name that you&#39;re using that is
more feminine in your private life I
have a name that is my official name I&#39;m
not like Sheltering it&#39;s like not
private locked away but you&#39;re not
making a huge announcement a huge
announcement about it it&#39;s just for like
friends and families and and stuff like
that but Chris k-r-i-s is what you can
call me on the internet are you gonna
get angry when people use CH I don&#39;t
really care I mean you can it&#39;ll be
wrong right are you gonna feel like
people are dead naming you I mean like
in a in a way they&#39;re going to like try
to use it to dead name me but number one
I can&#39;t be audibly dead named so that&#39;s
pretty true it&#39;s pretty cool it&#39;s a
pretty pretty big clutch uh number two I
mean like I said I I have no shame with
like who I was I I think it&#39;s so cool
and interesting that it&#39;s like I was
Chris with a CH and then I put that to
rest and now I can finally be Chris with
a kid you have a permanent Archive of
who you were in your transitional period
and who you are now literally it&#39;s kind
of like the Mr Beast channel was
accidentally like my trans timeline it
was a documentary
so you&#39;ve changed your the way you
present you&#39;ve changed the name and the
things that you prefer people to call
you&#39;ve changed your pronouns yeah
have you changed your voice because I
know that that&#39;s something that trans
people also work towards I am working on
it
um So currently I&#39;m working with the
Seattle voice Labs um it&#39;s a Discord
server where they offer free lessons
they offer paid lessons but Claire she
is incredible she&#39;s been teaching me and
she really pushed me to do a voice like
today yeah she wanted you to do it she
thinks I&#39;m ready to do like do a do a
sentence to give it a little sneak peek
I could feel like myself by like
presenting the way I wanted to grow my
hair out but I would look back when I
got because I&#39;m a YouTuber I get
recorded a lot yeah I would look back
and I would be like that&#39;s me and in my
voice I would open my mouth and I&#39;d be
like that&#39;s not me do you want to say a
sentence or do you want to talk us
through the different types of things
that go into the voice I&#39;m gonna say a
sentence but I&#39;ll kind of also show you
like the process I have to do yeah I
think this will be the first time many
people watching this will have ever seen
the thought process behind so I&#39;m in a
newer stage I&#39;ve only been going for a
little bit so it&#39;s easier for me to find
that space that feminine Voice by doing
a warm-up it sounds goofy uh whenever I
do it at home I make sure all my doors
are locked so now you&#39;re gonna do it on
your camera do it on camera now there&#39;s
millions of people watching it yeah my
voice my voice instructor encouraged me
it won&#39;t sound perfect
um it probably will get picked on a
little bit but that&#39;s kind of what I
like doing is showing people the like
real the rawness of it you ready for the
voice I&#39;m ready if you are oh gosh we
might have to do a couple of things
that&#39;s fine that&#39;s fine all right yeah
all right
here you guys sure
hey Anthony congratulations on buying
Smosh
the most interesting part about seeing
that is it felt like there was like a
Sparkle in your eye something about it
was like you I could see this feeling of
you feeling like yourself yeah and and I
really like showing the process of like
how I get to that because like I think
for a lot of people they they don&#39;t want
people to you know hear that process and
that&#39;s completely understandable it&#39;s a
very vulnerable space yeah it takes a
lot of work to even like get to yourself
to the point where you can do that
sometimes without feeling like oh my God
like uh I don&#39;t want anybody to hear me
I don&#39;t it&#39;ll never sound right but I
want people to hear that because it&#39;s
like that shows you that it&#39;s like
people say oh you&#39;re faking your voice
no I just slid my voice into the right
place basically it&#39;s like I&#39;m as I get
better with it I won&#39;t have to basically
push my voice into that place I want it
to be you&#39;re training to get to the
point where it feels natural it&#39;s a
muscle and like every muscle the more
you work it the more you train it it&#39;s
gonna break down build back up get
stronger and it&#39;s going to become muscle
memory to do this thing right what are
you looking forward to most now that you
have fully come out as your truest
identity you feel confident in yourself
what&#39;s next and what are you looking
forward to it really feels like for the
first time like
I can do anything now I can be who I
want to be like I can
create a channel if I want to I can
write a book if I want to yes I can
maybe produce a film if I want to are
these are these hints I don&#39;t know maybe
no but maybe in the future but you
really do have endless possibilities
exactly because I&#39;m finally able to be
myself and that spills out into other
areas in my life so it&#39;s not that I&#39;m
just authentically trans now I&#39;m
authentically Chris in every single way
I&#39;m able to articulate my feelings I&#39;m
able to talk about what I want so I feel
like
the future is kind of whatever I want it
to be right now you feel more creatively
driven now I do I&#39;m really excited I
I&#39;ve never felt the motivation to get in
front of cameras like I do now
congratulations on everything and I
think that your story is incredibly
inspiring and I think you&#39;re going to
change a lot of people&#39;s lives just just
by authentically being yourself in the
face of
hundreds of millions of opinions and and
thoughts yeah well thank you Anthony and
thank you for using your channel to give
queer and trans people a safe place to
talk about us and well who we are and
just let us be ourselves
there&#39;s a lot of traditionally more
feminine ways to speak people used to
tell me I did that a lot and I got
self-conscious about it and I stopped
stop being yourself stop stop it talk
like more like men are men talk yes
straight men talk straight men talk slow
men talk angry or men talk okay yeah
that was even too funny yeah that was a
little bit too feminine yeah we were
showing too much emotion damn it get out
the only emotion you&#39;re allowed to show
is anger anger that&#39;s the only emotion
and fear and fear no real men don&#39;t get
that&#39;s good yeah Real Men Real Men punch
wall and breakfast